# TIAGO CORREIA

#### GAME DEVELOPER



- +315 933 181 888
- tiagocorreia00@gmail.com
- Q Lisbon, Portugal
- https://linguinii.github.io/

## SKILLS

- Python
- Java
- HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- SQL
- Unity, C#
- Blender

# EDUCATION

#### BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN INFORMATICS AND MULTIMEDIA ENGINEERING

Instituto Superior de Engenharia de Lisboa

2018 - Present

# SOFT-SKILLS

- Drivers License B1, B
- Rugby Coach sub 12 level
- Competitive Rugby player for 4 years

### PROFILE

I am a student in computer and multimedia engineering and I chose this BSc with the goal of becoming a game designer. At the moment I am working on finishing my BSc and I want to gain work experience in the area and eventually take a masters degree.

### EXPERIENCE

#### **VRCOP - APPROACHING A VEHICLE**

03/2023 - 07/2023

First Person Virtual Reality simulator developed in unity to simulate a checkpoint operation for educational purposes.

# BHELATH BCLOSE - SOFTWARE DEVELOPER AND PROJECT SUPERVISOR

11/2022 - 02/2023

Developed and implemented an Alexa Skill
Supervised the development of a mobile app

#### ADITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Course

- Blender: Character design, modeling, rigging and and animation
- Unity: Level design (terrain, lighting, sound, special effects, post processing), Character controller, NPC development (enemies, boss, extras), Game programming, UI programming
- Python: Object oriented programming. Image, Video and Audio Processing using matplotlib and opency. Machine learning algorithms using sklearn
- Java: Object oriented programming. Artificial Intelligence fundamentals based on search methods. Distributed Systems.
- Front-End: production of multimedia content (JavaScript, HTML, CSS). Database fundamentals (XML, XSLT, HTML)